Using document retrieval for a RAG chatbot is boring.

Instead generate a full-stack application from your docs, by plugging in document retrieval as a tool into Cursor or Windsurf (Codeium) through MCP.

This is a dope example by Marcus Schiesser 🔥
* We use LlamaCloud to get high-quality parsing/indexing/retrieval over the most complex financial reports. 
* By plugging it into a code assistant, it can dynamically fetch this context to build an entire interactive dashboard that can do direct comparisons between two different companies.

Check out the thread below 🧵

You can setup any LlamaCloud index through the UI: https://lnkd.in/g9Wpqn7w
Here's a repo of examples to get started! https://lnkd.in/gbAYfzHC