Build your own AI agent frontend that can connect to the thousands of MCP servers popping up! 

With LlamaIndex you can easily build your own multi-agent workflow and connect to any MCP server as a tool. Use our higher-level agent workflow abstractions, or build your own workflow from scratch.

Our core wrapper interface is: https://lnkd.in/g96DZS3w

We're consolidating examples of building both MCP clients and servers in this repo: https://lnkd.in/gwHSXbXw

Big shoutout to Laurie Voss for pulling this together.