Learn to 𝗯𝘂𝗶𝗹𝗱 𝗶𝘁 𝗿𝗶𝗴𝗵𝘁 on AWS 😎 with this secret 🤫 𝗳𝗿𝗲𝗲 course, 🤑 𝗳𝗿𝗲𝗲 exam & 🎖️ 𝗳𝗿𝗲𝗲 Credly 𝗯𝗮𝗱𝗴𝗲 🔗 https://lnkd.in/gUSTTVbS


❓ Do you want to learn how to build secure, reliable, performant, cost effective and sustainable applications on AWS?

❓ Are you willing to take 2 FREE courses to study?

❓ Do you want to pass a free exam and get a Credly badge to prove your skillz?

✔️ Then this is the right course for you:

1️⃣ Login to Skill Builder by AWS Training & Certification:

2️⃣ 𝗘𝗡𝗥𝗢𝗟𝗟 into the AWS Well-Architected Foundations course: 
https://lnkd.in/gUSTTVbS 

3️⃣ Complete the course modules: 🤓 
Module 2 - How to Run a Well-Architected Framework Review
Module 3 - Deep Dive on the AWS Well-Architected Tool
Module 4 - Deep Dive on the Operational Excellence Pillar
Module 5 - Deep Dive on the Security Pillar
Module 6 - Deep Dive on the Reliability Pillar
Module 7 - Deep Dive on the Performance Efficiency Pillar
Module 8 - Deep Dive on the Cost Optimization Pillar
Module 9 - Deep Dive on the Sustainability Pillar

5️⃣ Complete the AWS Well-Architected Framework Course Assessment at the end of the AWS Well-Architected Foundations course. You got this! 😎💪

6️⃣ You will receive an email from the badge platform, Credly Acclaim, 10-14 days after passing the assessment to redeem and share your badge. 🎖️ 

7️⃣ Share your badge 🎖️ on LinkedIn ❤️‍🔥 and tag me so I can spread the word of your achievements! 😎