MCP or Model Context Protocol provides a unified interface to connect your Agents to external data sources, APIs and tools.

Today we're building a custom MCC server, which connects to Cursor and lets it perform deep web searches, as well as RAG over a specified directory.

Cursor IDE is our MCP host and we connect it to our custom server which has two tools.

Tech stack for the tools:

- Linkup to build for deep web search
- LlamaIndex workflows to enable RAG

100% open-source code with a step-by-step guide, link in the comments!