We've teamed up with Google Cloud to simplify building AI agents using the Gen AI Toolbox for Databases!

Gen AI Toolbox for Databases handles complex database connections, security, and tool management. 

Learn more about this integration and how to get started:
https://lnkd.in/ehMkSENf

Or head straight to the quickstart:
https://lnkd.in/ez-33CQ3

Learn more about GenAI Toolbox:
https://lnkd.in/eB4nC6wf