It's MCP week apparently! Yesterday we showed you how to use LlamaCloud as an MCP server, today see how to use LlamaIndex as a client to any MCP server! 
 
MCP allows you to create agents in LlamaIndex that can use any of hundreds of existing MCP servers as tools, radically expanding the utility of the agents you can build. 
 
Getting it working in LlamaIndex is just a few lines of code! 
 
Check out our open source MCP demo repo here: 
https://lnkd.in/g9wa-U4h 
 
Install the MCP client integration here: 
https://lnkd.in/gY4ezNni 
 
Learn more about Model Context Protocol: 
https://lnkd.in/ep3AQhqT